Then we'll run.
Let's go!
Mt. Fuji?
Hina Kawada Hina's Hinasanpo-
Hello, I'm Hina Kawada from Hinatazaka46!
Where am I this time?
I'm at the foot of Mt.
And guess what time it is?
It's pitch-dark here, but what's the time right now?
It's 2:40.
The reason why I want to climb Mt. Takao at this time of night is because I have always wanted to win in the morning.
Takao in the morning, I think I will arrive at the mountain just as it gets light in the morning, so I thought I would have a coffee while watching the sunrise.
I would like to drink coffee and eat breakfast while watching the sunrise.
I said I wanted to know about the morning victory, but it was a little earlier than I expected.
I said so myself.
Well, it will be fun, won't it?
Well then, let's pray for the safety of this trip.
I'd like to say a prayer for the safety of this Hina Walk.
Kawada Hina's Hina Walk, may she climb safely.
I beg you.
I've sunk. I mean, this is the first time I've been here Sakamoto-san.
I'm looking forward to it.
Ew.
It's too dark.
Oh!
Trees.
Nature.
I mean, it smells outside, too.
It's so...
I'll use the camera light to illuminate it.
I wonder if there are any insects.
It's like Ghibli.
It's like Ghibli!
It's starting to look like a hill.
Just a little bit.
It's quite a slope.
It's getting warmer.
It's fine.
Just now...
I was shivering.
It's pretty hot right now.
I've been walking for about half an hour now.
I feel like I've been walking for half an hour.
Feeling...
Phew.
Mmm-hmm.
Whew.
I'm a little tired.
Mm-hmm.
Phew.
I'm going to take a break.
But it looks like a bench.
I wonder if it's wet.
Oh, it's a little damp, but that's okay.
Here we go.
Oh!
Looks wet.
Let's just... let's just roll over here.
Oh!
That's a good idea.
You've got a lot of your strength back.
Oh! Beautiful! Oh, my gosh!
That's amazing! Because this is twice as expensive as the rest.
Let's find some more.
Oh!
We're almost halfway there.
We just walked here.
That's almost there.
Oh, we've walked that far already.
I guess it's all over now.
I feel like I'm done.
Heh heh heh
Wow! The stars are amazing, guys.
Can I turn off the light for a second? Here.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my gosh!
What shall we eat?
Wow.
Late night shopping.Late Night Shopping
Bon appétit!
Mmm.
Delicious!
I'm curious about this one.
Wow, I like it. Sweets on the mountain. In the mountains.
Yum! Delicious!
It's mahabi. Yes!
It's pretty spicy.
It's good to eat alternately, isn't it?
Salty and sweet.
Then, ah!
Oh, I'll be in trouble if I drop my camera.
Wow.
Tokyo is so big.
Wow, can you see this?
I'll have to put money in to see it.
Wow!
Tokyo Tower Sky Tree.
Is that the Sky Tree?
Wow!
Hmmm... Shinjuku.
Shinjuku is far from here.
Yokohama? Can you see it?
That's Yokohama?
So close. So close.
Good evening.
I'm so happy.
I'm okay, I guess I'm already up there.
Today, I'm wearing this, a hoodie, a T-shirt, and a midi-sleeve.
I'm also wearing these shoes, which are very comfortable shoes.
I'm not even wearing a hat.
Ta-da!
Mountain climbing style!
One of my favorite things today is
These socks!
Colorful socks!
The color alone is enough to cheer me up!
Socks are often hidden by pants
You can't see them.
I always wear strange socks.
The other day, my mom left them behind.
She sent me a pair of socks with a blue devil and a red devil on them.
All the way from Yamaguchi.
They were cute!
Oh, an octopus!
This one!
It's like this! Shipping!
Okay, I'm off then.
Hinatazaka46 May the sun shine on you many more times!
Sounds like a hit gigan
Kaiun
Hmm? Where are you? Where are we?
Oh, we're almost there.
I'll be up these stairs in three seconds.
Heh heh heh.
Oh, but it's a pretty gentle staircase.
It's nice.
Wow, it's all of a sudden...
Suddenly it feels like a mountain.
It feels like climbing a mountain!
Here we go!
Thank you for your hard work!
I feel like I've been crabby since a while ago.
I'm going to walk like an idol.
Here we go.
Oh!
Almost there.
Almost there, isn't it? This is...
It's so bright.
Is the sun coming up already? Not yet.
I think we're at the top.
Is this it?
Oh, wait.
I'm just having fun... getting my mind ready.
Good night.
Okay, let's run.
Let's go!
I think it's gone.
Here it comes!Here they come!
Wow!
That's great.
I'm so impressed!
The summit of Mt. Takao!
Wow!
Beautiful.
May I sit down for a moment?
Wow!
I guess you could call it a horizon, huh?
Oh, my God.
Amazing.
Impressive
Feels good
Mountains over there
Wow!
It's a mountain.
Oh, uh, what?
Mt Fuji?
It's so close! Wow!
This beautiful Mt. Fuji is amazing!
Kaa! I'm so impressed!
Cutting butter
I'm always so inefficient at cooking.
Well, I guess I can't do that anymore, can I?
Where are we gonna put it?
Where do I put it?
I'm so bad at cracking eggs.
I'll just close them up.
I don't know if I'll be able to do it.
It smells good.
I'd like to eat this.
It's a hot sandwich.
I want to try it as is.
Oh, wow.
Eggs.
Ta-da!
Oh, wow.
Looks so good. This is so good.
Today's star of the show is this bread. Bread.
I'm going to make hot sandwiches, so I'm going to put it on.
I'm nervous.
Oh, wow, this is how we're going to make ham, cheese and bacon hot sandwiches.
So we're going to put cheese on it.
Cheese.
Too much cheese. It's for fried eggs.
Let's put it on.
Which one do you want?
I'll put a lot of cheese on it.
You're terrible at this.
Too much?
Too much.
This one?
Is it really this thick?
I'll put it between these.
I can crush it, right? This one.
That's great.
Here.
Like this.
Sorry.
Yes, ma'am.
Can we really do this? It's kind of sticking out.
Wow! I was so surprised to see the sun in your eyes.
Wow!
I'll try to open it a little.
Ohhh!
Are you okay?
Wow!
Ohhh!
Is it normal? Normal?
Uh-oh.
Ooh.
Let's take a peek.
Mmm-hmm.
Oh.
Looks good.
Ta-da!
Oh, wow.
It looks good, doesn't it?
This is...
It's a success, isn't it?Success, right?
And you know what?
From your home
Honey tea.
I made it.
I'll have a sip.
[Hajime Shacho's ending]
I'm going to shime. Delicious!
Bon appétit!
Yum! Delicious!
I added a lot of mayonnaise.
It's that much, but it's delicious!
I don't know why I can't cook well.
Delicious!
I'm going to finish. Delicious!
Next time, I want to go far away and eat dumplings and stuff.
I want to eat a lot of food already!
I want to go on a gourmet trip!